Hi Ariff BAKRI

**** 017-3738299

□ ariffbakri17@gmail.com

linkedin.com/m/ariff-bakri-2a95a9238

🦞 Kelantan Malaysia



INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

About Me

A detailed and highly capable IT Professional with experience performing imaging or remaging for company laptops and desktops as well as troubleshooting technical issues. Also experienced in development a software, installing, maintaining and providing support for computer systems and network.

Education

2020 - Sultan Idris Education University

Present Bachelor of Education in

Information Technology (Hons)

2018 - 2019 STPM in Sekolah Menengah

Kebangsaan Kubang Kerian

CGPA 2.84

2013 - 2017 School at Sekolah Menengah

Kebangsaan Kubang Kerian

Experience

2020 -Present Junior Web Developer

Created a software, physical, prototype design and functions for websites. Registered official online projects with search engines for optimized website traffic.

2019 -2020

Editor Video, Poster and Photographer

Editing the video for marketing of mini, small, and medium cafe.

Making a poster and banner to promote the cafe.

Worked with the designer team to build cafe website.

Skills

Web Design 90%
Coding 85%
Database 85%
R&D 85%
Teamwork 85%